konami.com 2015-09-06

# Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.| Privacy Policy

Last Updated:  **December 7, 2013**

By using the Online Services (as defined below), or otherwise providing your personally identifiable information to Konami, you consent to the collection and use of such personally identifiable information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with any information and do not use the Online Services.

Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc. (“Konami”, “we” or “our”) has adopted this Privacy Policy to describe how we collect, use, safeguard and disclose the information you provide to Konami. This policy may be revised from time to time, so please revisit this page often to remain fully informed of our policies.

This Privacy Policy and the certification seal located on this page confirms that Konami is a valid licensee and participating member in the Entertainment Software Rating Board’s ESRB Privacy Certified Program. To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and all the Online Services have been reviewed and certified by ESRB Privacy Certified Program to meet established online information collection and use practices. As part of this privacy program, we are subject to frequent audits of the Online Services and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB.

ESRB Privacy Certified Program is a third-party seal provider whose mission is to protect consumers’ online privacy and make the Internet a secure, reliable, and private place to share information and conduct business. ESRB Privacy Certified Program promotes and enforces established principles and guidelines for fair information practices that include requirements of full disclosure, notice, and informed consent.

Whenever you visit a website or page that displays the ESRB Privacy Certified Program certification seal, you can expect to be notified of the following:

  * The websites, pages and information covered by the Privacy Policy;
  * Exactly what information may be collected and how it will be used;
  * The consequences, if any, resulting from your refusal to provide personally identifiable information;
  * Whether a company uses cookies, tracks IP addresses, or uses other passive means to collect technical information;
  * Who, if anyone, is collecting your personally identifiable information;
  * With whom, if anyone, is your personally identifiable information shared;
  * What a company’s policy is regarding links to third party sites;
  * What choices you have with regard to the use of your personally identifiable information;
  * How you can access, and if necessary, change the personally identifiable information a company collects and maintains;
  * How a company ensures data security, quality, and integrity; and
  * Where and how to ask questions or file complaints.

**The websites, pages and information covered by this Privacy Policy:**

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected through (a) the website located at www.konami.com; (b) all related Konami-controlled websites; (c) our pages on social media websites such as Facebook, Twitter and Google+ (the “Konami Social Media Pages”); (d) any software applications that we make available through the Konami Social Media Pages; (e) our downloadable interactive mobile applications; and (f) our other online products or offerings (collectively, the foregoing items (a) through (f) shall be referred to as the “Online Services”). Please note that through our Konami Social Media Pages, we may collect personally identifiable information from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy; however, this Privacy Policy does not govern the collection, use or disclosure of information by any third party, including without limitation social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter and Google+ or third party service providers such as Apple, Google or mobile service providers. We recommend that you independently review the privacy policies of these third parties. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE DATA COLLECTION, USAGE AND DISCLOSURE POLICIES AND PRACTICES OF SOCIAL MEDIA ONLINE SERVICES OR ANY OTHER THIRD PARTY.

Some jurisdictions also may require notice concerning personally identifiable information collected offline; for those jurisdictions, this Privacy Policy also explains our practices regarding personally identifiable information that we obtain from offline sources, such as written or verbal communications.

Please note,the information obtained through Konami Style Store, located at <https://shop.konami.com/>, is held by by Arvato Digital Services LLC and is therefore governed by the Arvato Privacy Policy.

**What types of information does Konami collect and how will it be used?**

Konami may collect information about you when you use the Online Services or our products or services, or when you otherwise provide personally identifiable information to us. For example, we may obtain personally identifiable information through: (1) “community” registration (e.g., registration for online games or tournaments, to participate in forums or chat rooms, to receive ongoing marketing or other information, etc.); (2) product registration; (3) email correspondence with product support/customer service; (4) polls or surveys; (5) E-Cards or “Send-to-a-Friend” emails; (6) the Konami Social Media Pages; (7) software applications that we make available through the Konami Social Media Pages and/or mobile services/application; (8) information submitted in a business capacity (e.g., resumes); and/or (9) information submitted as part of a promotion (e.g., online contests or sweepstakes). The types of information that may be requested for each activity and the way the information may be used are detailed below.

§ Community Registration

If you choose to register on the Online Services, you will be required to provide your first and last name, city, state, zip code, country of residence, email address, date of birth, age, occupation and a user name and password. In addition, you may be asked to provide other information, such as your phone number, the provision of which is optional. The information that you submit during registration will: (a) make up your profile; (b) allow you to use our message board and participate in other activities on the Online Services (e.g., promotions or game-specific events); and (c) allow us to send you, via email, news about products, features and enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, and contents and events of interest. Please note that the information (e.g., email address, username, occupation, and interests) contained in your profile (i.e., that you provide when registering) may be viewable to other users of Konami’s message board. We cannot and do not guarantee that this information will be kept confidential or private. If you choose, you may omit from your profile certain information that you do not want the public to see by leaving such information blank at the time of registration, or choosing to make your email address not accessible via such message boards.

§ Product Registration

To register a Konami product on the Online Services, you will be required to submit your first and last name, city, state, zip code, country of residence, email address, date of birth, age and occupation. You may also be asked to provide your phone number and answer demographic questions relating to your age, information about the product you purchased, the type of console you own, and the types of games you enjoy playing. The information that you submit during product registration will entitle you to limited warranty protection and technical support. Unless you opt out at the time of registration, we may also use your registration information to send you, via email, news about products, features and enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, and contents and events of interest. You may also choose to opt out at any time from receiving these messages, as described below.

§ Customer Support

Konami may collect, use and store personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit to us via email or other means when contacting Konami customer service or support. For example, we may provide on the Online Services a link through which an online visitor can send e-mail to customer service addressing any issue a user encounters with a Konami product. Your email address and any personally identifiable information you choose to provide in the body of such email is used by Konami for purposes of addressing and responding to your question. Although most e-mail messages are deleted immediately after they are responded to, in certain cases, hard copies or data from certain e-mail correspondence may be kept on file for security or other business purposes, and even deleted emails may remain archived or in system backups. Any such copy or data will be stored in a secure location, and information from these messages will not be used for marketing purposes. Our policy is not to retain any email addresses collected from you during the use of the E-Cards or “Send-to-a-Friend” email feature on any Online Services, as these email addresses are only intended to be used to send a one-time email notification on your behalf.

§ Polls/Surveys

From time to time, we may ask you for your opinion about certain matters in the form of online or offline polls or surveys, including your opinion with respect to our games or other products and services. Your responses to these polls help us provide products and services of interest to you. While we may ask for certain demographic or other information in connection with such polls or surveys to allow us to better interpret the results, we do not request personally identifiable information, such as your name, in connection with these polls or surveys.

§ Konami Social Media Pages

You do not have to provide personally identifiable information to use the Konami Social Media Pages. However, in order for you to take advantage of particular opportunities provided through the Konami Social Media Pages (for example, promotions, events, games or other applications), we may require that you furnish personally identifiable information. We and our third-party service providers collect such information from you through the Konami Social Media Pages, including your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, Facebook and other social media IDs and the names of your friends, only when voluntarily provided to us (either directly or indirectly as a result of Facebook or other social media site being authorized to submit such information to us). Such information may be used and disclosed for any purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy. Konami also collects other information (such as your gender, social media networks, workplace, geographic location, application settings and statistics, status updates, user interactions and other non-personally identifiable information) when you voluntarily provide such information to us (either directly or indirectly as a result of Facebook or other social media Online Services being authorized to submit such information to us). Unless otherwise noted, we may share, use and disclose such information for any purpose in our discretion.

§ Promotions

From time to time, we may offer you the opportunity to enter into Konami-sponsored promotions, such as contests or sweepstakes. We may offer these promotions through our Online Services or in-person. To participate in a promotion, you may be required to submit information, such as your first and last name, city, state, zip code, country of residence, email address, date of birth, and age, so that we (or our partners) can administer the promotion. For example, we (or our partners) may use this information to determine whether you are eligible to participate in the promotion and/or to notify you in the event you are selected as a winner.

§ Mobile Services and Applications

Certain of our mobile services and/or applications may require that you furnish personally identifiable information by downloading the application to your mobile device. We and third-party service providers collect such information from you through your mobile device, including your name, user name, profile pictures, telephone number, device identifiers, e-mail address, contacts, GPS location, browser history, chat or messaging activity, application linked friends and Apple Game Center ID. Certain collection of information may be disabled or limited in specific applications in the user settings. Such information may be used and disclosed for any purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy. Konami also collects other non-personally identifiable information. Unless otherwise noted, we may share, use and disclose such non-personally identifiable information for any purpose in our discretion.

§ Candidates for Employment

Konami may provide on the Online Services an email address that visitors can use to send us their resumes. In the future we may expand functionality on the Online Services for other similar business uses. We also may collect personally identifiable information offline about candidates for employment. Personally identifiable information about candidates will be used for the purpose of accepting and evaluating candidate submissions for job postings and may therefore be shared within our company. If the candidate becomes an employee, this information also may be used and retained for employment purposes. Other than as explained in this paragraph, this Privacy Policy does not apply to personally identifiable information gathered concerning job applicants or candidates for employment.

§ Passive Collection

As noted below, (see “Does Konami use cookie, track IP addresses or use other passive means to collect information?”), we use certain passive means to collect information regarding visitors to the Online Services, Online Services traffic patterns and Online Services usage. Unless noted otherwise, we may share, use and disclose such information, as well as aggregated information or other non-personal information, for any purpose in our discretion.

§ Other Uses of Personally Identifiable Information

We may also use your personally identifiable and demographic information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs. From time to time, we are approached by third-party companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. To extend these products or services to you, we may use your personally identifiable information to send out notices on their behalf. We strive to limit the notices and communications to those that we think you would appreciate receiving.

Your personally identifiable information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using the Online Services, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules than in your country.

**No matter what method we use to collect information and no matter how we use that information, we seek only to collect the information that we believe is reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.**

**What happens if I refuse to provide my personally identifiable information to Konami?**

If you choose not to submit personally identifiable information when requested, you may not be able to participate in certain activities on the Online Services which may considerably limit the services we can provide you. For example, if you refuse to provide your email address when registering, you will not be able to use our message boards.

**Does Konami use cookies, track IP addresses or use other passive means to collect information?**

Cookies

Konami may collect information through cookies to improve the use of the Online Services. A “cookie” is a small string of text sent by the Online Services to your browser and then stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize and enhance your experience on the Online Services, and to help us diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Online Services. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name and date of birth, tell us that you have visited the Online Services before, track your usage of the Online Services, and may contain information that will make your next visit to the Online Services more enjoyable. In addition, Konami will not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. However, rejecting cookies may prevent you from taking advantage of certain portions of the Online Services.

Third Party Cookies

We currently contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of third parties for marketing purposes to help us to deliver advertisements and to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use the Online Services. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on the Online Services. We may collect the following types of information through such third party cookies: the activity of the Online Services’ visitors’ browsers when the visitors are viewing the Online Services; the website path of visitors; the time visitors come to the Online Services; and product codes and pricing information for merchandise that visitors purchase via the Online Services. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products or Online Services most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from the Online Services on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. If you do not want to help us learn how to improve the Online Services and our products, offers and marketing strategy, you can “opt-out” of our ability to analyze such data by emailing [kdeonline@konami.com](mailto:kdeonline@konami.com). You may also opt-out of having your information tracked for marketing purposes by following the instructions provided [here](http://www.adtech.com/en/service/cookies.html). You may also opt-out of receiving this and other targeted advertising by following the link [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

IP Addresses

While you are browsing the Online Services, Konami automatically collects your IP address and your activity while using the Online Services. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

Log Files

Konami also collects information in the form of log files that record activity on the Online Services, including how many “hits” a particular web page is getting (a.k.a. “click-through data”). For example, log file entries are generated every time a visitor clicks an image on the Online Services. These entries enable Konami to assess overall site activity, track interest in particular portions of the Online Services, troubleshoot technical concerns, and identify the type of browser you are using. We may also use the log file entries for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the products and services we provide you. Log files are used internally only.

**Who is collecting my personally identifiable information?**

The information that you disclose to us while visiting any of the Online Services or by downloading a mobile application is collected by Konami, a third party service provider or one of its vendors on Konami’s behalf, and is used in the manner specified above. PLEASE BE AWARE THAT BY DISCLOSING CERTAIN INFORMATION ON THE KONAMI SOCIAL MEDIA PAGES, YOU ARE ALSO DISCLOSING THIS INFORMATION TO THE APPLICABLE SOCIAL MEDIA SITE. SIMILARLY, BY DISCLOSING CERTAIN INFORMATION ON THE MOBILE APPLICATIONS, YOU ARE ALSO DISCLOSING THIS INFORMATION TO THE APPLICABLE MOBILE SERVICE PROVIDER AND/OR APPLICATION DOWNLOAD PORTAL (I.E., APPLE AND/OR GOOGLE). WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE DATA COLLECTION, USAGE AND DISCLOSURE POLICIES AND PRACTICES OF SUCH SOCIAL MEDIA SITES AND THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS. The information obtained through Konami Style Store by Arvato Digital Services LLC is governed by the Arvato Privacy Policy.

**With whom does Konami share my personally identifiable information?**

Except as expressly provided in this Privacy Policy, Konami’s policy is to not sell, rent, or disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties. Konami may share your personally identifiable information with the following parent, subsidiary, and/or affiliate companies [http://www.konami.com/sitelist/](http://www.konami.com/sitelist.php), for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including to allow them to send you information about their own products and services. Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc. is the party responsible for the management of this jointly-used information.

From time to time, Konami may share your personally identifiable information with its third-party service providers and/or licensors, to enable them to provide services in connection with the operation, maintenance and/or support of the Konami Online Services. Such services may include, without limitation, message board operation, email delivery, product registration, storage, website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, infrastructure provision, IT support, customer support, credit card processing and web site auditing.

We may use and disclose the information we maintain, including personally identifiable information, (a) when required to do so by law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from a law enforcement agency or public or government authority, including outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (d) to protect the rights, property, or safety of Konami, our customers, users of the Online Services or others; and (e) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

In addition, Konami may disclose personally identifiable information and other information we obtain from you to a third party in the event of a reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock.

**What is Konami’s policy regarding children?**

Konami does not permit children under 13 years of age to become registered users of the Online Services, and we do not collect information from children through the Online Services. By using any portion of the Online Services, you represent that you are not under 13 years of age.

**What is Konami’s policy regarding links to third party sites?**

You should be aware that while you are on the Online Services, Konami may reference or provide links to third party sites. Konami does not control, nor are we responsible for, the privacy policies or information practices of such third parties or their websites. Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of such third party websites, we recommend that you read the privacy policies posted on these sites before you submit any personally identifiable information via such third party sites.

**Can I choose how my personally identifiable information is used?**

If you do not want Konami to send you marketing communications and/or if you prefer not to have Konami share your personally identifiable information with its affiliates for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us, at any time, via e-mail at [kdeonline@konami.com](mailto:kdeonline@konami.com) . Alternatively, we will be happy to honor any such opt-out requests made by regular mail to:

**Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.**  
Attention: Website Administrator  
2381 Rosecrans Ave. Suite #200  
El Segundo, CA 90245

We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that if you do opt out of receiving marketing-related messages from us, we may still send you important administrative messages as permitted by applicable law.

**How can I access my personally identifiable information?**

It is important to maintain the accuracy of your personally identifiable information that may be collected from you on the Online Services. We will use our commercially reasonable efforts to respond promptly to update our database when you tell us the information in our database is not accurate. It is your responsibility to ensure that such information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you have registered to use the message board on certain of the Online Services and wish to update your profile, you may do so online by visiting the “profile” section found at each game forum on certain of the Online Services. You may be required to submit your login name and password before you can access your profile information.

If you wish to review, update, or delete any other personally identifiable information that we may have collected about you, please contact us via e-mail at[kdeonline@konami.com](mailto:kdeonline@konami.com), or by regular mail at:

**Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.**  
Attention: Website Administrator  
2381 Rosecrans Ave. Suite #200  
El Segundo, CA 90245

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Currently, Konami does not disclose personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

**What safeguards does Konami use to protect my personally identifiable information?**

Konami maintains appropriate safeguards that ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the personally identifiable information we collect from our users. Personally identifiable information collected by Konami is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public and is only accessible by authorized employees. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control (i.e., maintain data quality). Before we allow users of the Online Services to access their personally identifiable information, for example, we verify their identity by prompting them to submit information such as their login name and password.

Nonetheless, please be aware that Internet data transmission is not always secure and we cannot warrant or guarantee that information you transmit utilizing the Online Services is secure. Because security is important to both Konami and you, we will always make reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems.

**How do I ask a question or file a complaint?**

If you have any questions, complaints or comments regarding our Privacy Policy Statement or practices, please contact us via email at [kdeonline@konami.com](mailto:kdeonline@konami.com) or by regular mail at:

**Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.**  
Attention: Website Administrator  
2381 Rosecrans Ave. Suite #200  
El Segundo, CA 90245

You can also contact ESRB Privacy Certified Program directly at[www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.jsp](http://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.jsp)or at:

ESRB  
Attn: Privacy Certified Program  
317 Madison Avenue, 22nd Floor  
New York, NY 10017  

**Effectiveness of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of **December 7, 2013**. We reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, update or make changes to this policy and any such modifications, alterations, updates or changes will be effective upon posting. Please check back from time to time to ensure you aware of these changes. In the event we modify this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting a notice on the homepage of our Online Services or by emailing you. Your continued use of the Online Services will signify your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.
